<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<newsBunch>
	<news>
		<date>17 January, 2025 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Traffic Accident Detection via Fusion-GRU based Future Frame Detection Box Prediction&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://icc2025.ieee-icc.org/&quot;&gt;IEEE ICC 2025&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Ziyuan!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 December, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>We have two papers accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ieee-aiplus.org/2024/trustcom/&quot;&gt;IEEE TrustCom 2025&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Tongxi and Spyridon!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 December, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Towards Alarm Reduction in Intrusion Detection: A Recurrent Neural Network Approach&quot; has been Published by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ieee-hust-ncc.org/2024/HPCC/&quot;&gt;IEEE HPCC 2025&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Xiaofu!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>05 November, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Blockchain-Driven Distributed Edge Intelligence for Enhanced Internet-of-Vehicles&quot; has been Published by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/10744213&quot;&gt;IEEE IoTJ&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Xiaofu!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>23 September, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;BANN-TMGuard: Toward Touch-Movement-Based Screen Unlock Patterns via Blockchain-Enabled Artificial Neural Networks on IoT Devices&quot; has been Published by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/10685479&quot;&gt;IEEE IoTJ &lt;/a&gt;. </content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>23 August, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;DEMO: Towards A Novel Ultrasonic Side-channel Attack on Mobile Devices&quot; has been published by &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3672202.3673730&quot;&gt;ACM SIGCOMM 2024&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Yingli!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>23 July, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Pitfalls of data masking techniques: Re-identification attacks&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://securecomm.eai-conferences.org/2024/&quot;&gt;SecureComm 2024&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Brooke and Andreas!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>23 June, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;can-sleuth: Investigating and Evaluating Automotive Intrusion Detection Datasets&quot; has been published by &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3655693.3655696&quot;&gt;EICC 2024&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Brooke!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>23 June, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;UltraCommander: Ultrasonic Side Channel Attack via Browser Extensions&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-981-97-8540-7_12&quot;&gt;DSPP 2024&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Yingli!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 May, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>We have two papers accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ispec2024.github.io/ISPEC2024/&quot;&gt;ISPEC 2024 &lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Kanagaratnam and Rishikesh!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 May, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;can-fp: An attack-aware analysis of false alarms in automotive intrusion detection models&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computer.org/csdl/proceedings-article/pst/2024/10788039/22IRQWyql8I&quot;&gt;PST 2024&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Brooke!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 May, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;can-train-and-test: A curated CAN dataset for automotive intrusion detection&quot; has been Published by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0167404824000786&quot;&gt;Computers and Security &lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Brooke!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>08 March, 2024 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Detecting Post Editing of Multimedia Images using Transfer Learning and Fine Tuning&quot; has been Published by &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3633284&quot;&gt;ACM TOMM&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Simon and Malthe!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 October, 2023 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Securing IoT Firmware Dispatch System With Blockchain&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ieee-cybermatics.org/2023/blockchain/&quot;&gt;IEEE Blockchain 2023&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Vince and Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 August, 2023 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Securing Offshore Installations Against Automatic Identification System Spoofing&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://globecom2023.ieee-globecom.org/&quot;&gt;IEEE Globecom 2023&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Grzegorz and Brooke!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 August, 2023 00:00:00</date>
		<content>We have two survey papers accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comsoc.org/publications/journals/ieee-comst&quot;&gt;IEEE COMST&lt;/a&gt; &#40;&quot;Intrusion Detection in the Automotive Domain: A Comprehensive Review&quot;&#41; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/journal/expert-systems-with-applications&quot;&gt;Expert Systems with Applications&lt;/a&gt; &#40;&quot;A Survey of Deep Learning-based Intrusion Detection in Automotive Application&quot;&#41;. Congratulations Brooke!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 June, 2023 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Towards Quantifying Cross-Domain Maximal Extractable Value for Blockchain Decentralisation&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://icics23.nankai.edu.cn/&quot;&gt;ICICS 2023&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Johan!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 June, 2023 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;NoSneaky: A Blockchain-based Execution Integrity Protection Scheme in Industry 4.0&quot; has been published by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ieee-ies.org/pubs/transactions-on-industrial-informatics&quot;&gt;IEEE Transactions on Industrial Informatics&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 March, 2023 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;No Free Wireless Charge: Covert Channels via Wireless Charging on Mobile Devices&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://dsn2023.dei.uc.pt/&quot;&gt;IEEE DSN 2023.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 November, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;FolketID: A Decentralized Blockchain-based NemID Alternative against DDoS Attacks&quot; has received the Best Paper Award from &lt;a href=&quot;https://provsec2023.github.io/ProvSec2023/&quot;&gt;ProvSec 2023&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 October, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Towards A Scalable and Privacy-Preserving Blockchain-based European Parking System&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;http://ieee-icpads.net/2022/&quot;&gt;ICPADS 2022&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Jonathan!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 September, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Towards Enhanced EEG-based Authentication with Motor Imagery Brain-Computer Interface&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.acsac.org/2022/&quot;&gt;ACSAC 2022.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Bingkun!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 August, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;A Practical Blockchain-based Maintenance Record System for Better Aircraft Security&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://scisec.org/scisec2022/&quot;&gt;SciSec 2022&lt;/a&gt;, and received the Best Paper Award. Congratulations Wictor, Sille and Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 August, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our three papers &quot;IDS for CAN: A Practical Intrusion Detection System for CAN Bus Security&quot;, &quot;Towards Artificial Neural Network Based Intrusion Detection with Enhanced Hyperparameter Tuning&quot; and &quot;TDL-IDS: Towards A Transfer Deep Learning based Intrusion Detection System&quot; have been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://globecom2022.ieee-globecom.org/&quot;&gt;IEEE GLOBECOM 2022.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Brooke, Andrei and Xingguo!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 June, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;DevLeChain - An Open Blockchain Development Platform for Decentralized Applications&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ieee-cybermatics.org/2022/blockchain/&quot;&gt;IEEE Blockchain 2022&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 June, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Mosaic - A Blockchain Consensus Algorithm Based on Random Number Generation&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ieee-cybermatics.org/2022/blockchain/&quot;&gt;IEEE Blockchain 2022&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Zhengzhong!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 June, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Security Analysis in Satellite Communication based on Geostationary Orbit&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pstnet.ca/&quot;&gt;PST 2022.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Jacob and Mikkel!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 June, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Designing In-Air Hand Gesture-based User Authentication System via Convex Hull&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pstnet.ca/&quot;&gt;PST 2022.&lt;/a&gt;  Congratulations Yiming!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 March, 2022 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our AirChain project will give a demo in &lt;a href=&quot;https://icbc2022.ieee-icbc.org/&quot;&gt;IEEE ICBC 2022&lt;/a&gt;!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 November, 2021 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our BlockCycle project has received the Honorary Mention Award for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comsoc.org/membership/ieee-comsoc-student-competition&quot;&gt;IEEE ComSoc Student Competition&lt;/a&gt; "Communications Technology Changing the World" 2021. Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 September, 2021 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Towards DTW-based Unlock Scheme using Handwritten Graphics on Smartphones&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ieee-msn.org/2021/&quot;&gt;IEEE MSN 2021.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Li!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 September, 2021 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;BALSAPro: Towards A Security Protocol for Bluetooth Low Energy&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ieee-msn.org/2021/&quot;&gt;IEEE MSN 2021.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Mohamad!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 August, 2021 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;My Data, My Control: A Secure Data Sharing and Access Scheme over Blockchain&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/journal/journal-of-information-security-and-applications&quot;&gt;JISA (Elsevier)&lt;/a&gt;.</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 August, 2021 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;NGS: Mitigating DDoS Attacks using SDN-based Network Gate Shield&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://globecom2021.ieee-globecom.org/&quot;&gt;IEEE GLOBECOM 2021.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Suhel!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 August, 2021 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;ActAnyware - Blockchain-based Software Licensing Scheme&quot; has received the best paper award by &lt;a href=&quot;https://blocksys.info/2021/&quot;&gt;BlockSys 2021.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 May, 2021 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Mind the Amplification: Cracking Content Delivery Networks via DDoS Attacks&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;http://wasa-conference.org/WASA2021/&quot;&gt;WASA 2021.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Zihao!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 April, 2021 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Mind the Scraps: Attacking Blockchain based on Selfdestruct&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://data61dsslab.github.io/acisp2021/&quot;&gt;ACISP 2021.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 December, 2020 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;NoPKI - A Point-to-Point Trusted Third Party Service based on Blockchain Consensus Algorithm&quot; has received the Best Paper Award by &lt;a href=&quot;https://link.springer.com/book/10.1007/978-981-15-9739-8&quot;&gt;FCS 2020.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 December, 2020 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our SpaCCS paper has received the Best Student Paper Award by &lt;a href=&quot;http://spaccs.org/SpaCCS2020/&quot;&gt;SpaCCS 2020.&lt;/a&gt; Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 November, 2020 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Towards Decentralized Bicycle Insurance System Based on Blockchain&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sigapp.org/sac/sac2021/&quot;&gt;ACM SAC 2021&lt;/a&gt;. Congratulations Wayne!</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 October, 2020 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;ChainPKI - Towards EThash-based Decentralized PKI with Privacy Enhancement&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ieeedsc.org/2021/&quot;IEEE DSC 2021.&lt;/a&gt;</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 October, 2020 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;I Can Think Like You! Towards Reaction Spoofing Attack on Brainwave-based Authentication&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;http://spaccs.org/SpaCCS2020/&quot;SpaCCS 2020.&lt;/a&gt;</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 October, 2019 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Evaluation of Anomaly-based Intrusion Detection with Combined Imbalance Correction and Feature Selection&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nsclab.org/nss2020/&quot;&gt;NSS 2020.&lt;/a&gt;</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 October, 2019 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Towards Secure Open Banking Architecture: An Evaluation with OWASP&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nsclab.org/nss2019/&quot;&gt;NSS 2019.&lt;/a&gt;.</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 May, 2019 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;CyberShip-IoT: A Dynamic and Adaptive SDN-Based Security Policy Enforcement Framework for Ships&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/journal/future-generation-computer-systems&quot;&gt;Future Generation Computer Systems.&lt;/a&gt;</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 July, 2018 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;CyberShip: An SDN-based Autonomic Attack Mitigation Framework for Ship Systems&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://scisec.org/scisec2018/index.html&quot;&gt;SciSec 2018.&lt;/a&gt;</content>
	</news>
	<news>
		<date>01 June, 2018 00:00:00</date>
		<content>Our paper &quot;Analyzing the Communication Security between Smartphones and IoT based on CORAS&quot; has been accepted by &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;NSS 2018.&lt;/a&gt;</content>
	</news>
</newsBunch>
